var questions = [{
  "question" : "What is the name of the CalTech seismologist who invented the scale used to measure the magnitude of earthquakes??",
  "option1" : "Charles Richter",
  "option2" : "Hiram Walker",
  "option3" : "Giuseppe Mercalli",
  "option4" : "Joshua Rumble",
  "answer" : "Charles Richter"
} , {
  "question" : "This statesman, politican, scholar, inventor, and one of early presidents of USA invented the swivel chair, the spherical sundial, the moldboard plow, and the cipher wheel.",
  "option1" : "George Washington",
  "option2" : "Alexander Hamilton",
  "option3" : "John Adams",
  "option4" : "Thomas Jefferson",
  "answer" : "Thomas Jefferson"
}, {
  "question" : "The radioactive element radium was invented by which of the following scientists?",
  "option1" : "Marie Curie",
  "option2" : "Benjamin Franklin",
  "option3" : "Albert Einstein",
  "option4" : "Isaac Newton",
  "answer" : "Marie Curie"

}, {
  "question" : "The most popular invention that is used in our day-to-day life called ballpoint pen was invented by which of the following scientists:",
  "option1" : "Waterman brothers",
  "option2" : "Write brothers",
  "option3" : "Biro brothers",
  "option4" : "Bicc brothers",
  "answer" : "Biro brothers"

}, {
  "question" : "Until Victorian times, chocolate was thought of as a drink. When did the first chocolate bar appear?",
  "option1" : "1828",
  "option2" : "1831",
  "option3" : "1825",
  "option4" : "There is no sure date",
  "answer" : "There is no sure date"

}, {
  "question" : "What 'game' was first produced by the Southern Novelty Company in Baltimore, Maryland in 1892?",
  "option1" : "Frisbee",
  "option2" : "Monopoly",
  "option3" : "Ouija board",
  "option4" : "Ping Pong",
  "answer" : "Ouija board"

}, {
  "question" : "Where was the yo-yo invented?",
  "option1" : "France",
  "option2" : "United States",
  "option3" : "Philippines",
  "option4" : "England",
  "answer" : "Philippines"

}, {
  "question" : "When were blue jeans invented?",
  "option1" : "1900s",
  "option2" : "1860s",
  "option3" : "1870s",
  "option4" : "1850s",
  "answer" : "1850s"

}, {
  "question" : "In which decade was the Internet first implemented?",
  "option1" : "1940s",
  "option2" : "1950s",
  "option3" : "1960s",
  "option4" : "1980s",
  "answer" : "1960s"

}, {
  "question" : "Who invented Bicycle?",
  "option1" : "Leo H Baekeland",
  "option2" : "Karl Benz",
  "option3" : "Evangelista Torricelli",
  "option4" : "Kirkpatrick Macmillan",
  "answer" : "Kirkpatrick Macmillan"

}
]
